



+32 473 121 73



pauline.valgaeren@outlook.be



https://portfoliopaulinevalgaeren .netlify.app



Zandstreep 90, 2450 Meerhout

## **SKILLS**

#### Personal skills:

- Ambitious
- Reliable
- Persevering
- Empathic
- Self-direction and development

### **Professional skills:**

- Web development
- Programming
- Database management
- DevOps
- Cybersecurity

# **LANGUAGES**







French

Dutch

English

# **PAULINE VALGAEREN**

## **STUDENT**

My name is Pauline Valgaeren and I am 21 years old. I am studying Cloud & Cyber Security at Thomas More in Geel. I am an enthusiastic and positive girl who does not shy away from opportunities. Learning and discovering new things is really something for me and I like to share my knowledge with others.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Nike

#### 2019 - Present

Since I was 18, I have been working at Nike in the summer as a student. Here I stand in the warehouse and make sure that packages are carefully sent to the right sender.

#### Mise en Place

# 2022-Present

Since April 2022, I have been working as a student at Mise en Place. This is an international catering agency with over 50 branches in 5 different countries. This job has helped me a lot in developing my social skills.

## **EDUCATION**

#### 2019-2021

Nutrition and dietetics - Thomas More

2 years completed

2021 - Present Cloud & Cyber Security - Thomas More